sony.co.in 2017-10-03

# Privacy Policy : Privacy Policy : Sony India

Your privacy is important to us. This is why, as a Sony customer, we are committed to the protection of your Privacy.

**We assure:**  
While offering you valued added service, our foremost interest is to reciprocate your faith.

  * We shall strive to safeguard your personal information and try to prevent any unauthorized use and / or access thereof.
  * We will limit the use of your personal information to the extent that we reasonably require, to deliver our products, services and other opportunities, and to administer our business.
  * We will permit only authorized employees, who are trained in proper handling of customer personal information, to have access to that information. Employees who violate our Privacy Policy will be subject to our normal disciplinary process.

  * We shall act upon your request, in writing, for any addition or modification of your personal information or any part thereof. You may Email us at [**Sonyindia.care@ap.sony.com**](mailto:Sonyindia.care@ap.sony.com) for any modifications/changes, if required.

  * Whenever we hire other organizations to provide support services that require sharing of personal information, we will require them to confirm to our privacy standards and allow us to audit them for compliance.

**How we use information**  
Your information is important to us at Sony. We shall use your information to provide you with quick and convenient access to you, to provide you with information about products & services and of new items of interest. We undertake not to divulge your information , save and except where we are required, by law, to respond to statutory authorities or direction of any Court or legal authority.
